https://nandivet.com/privacy-refund-policy/

We accept credit card payments from Visa, Mastercard, Discover and American ExpressPrivacy Policy We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm and continuing commitment to the privacy of personal information provided by those visiting and interacting with this web site. We hold the privacy of your personal information in the highest regard. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.We recognize the importance of protecting your privacy and our policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site. This policy will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers’ needs.Refund Policy Customers may request a refund or return for merchandise and goods within thirty days from purchase. However, Nandi Veterinary Associates reserves the right to analyze each request individually and determine if the refund or return is applicable. No refunds or returns are available or applicable to services provided by
Nandi Veterinary Associates
Close Font Resize A- A+ Keyboard navigation Readable FontContrast Choose color black white green blue red orange yellow navi Underline links Highlight Links Clear cookies Remove Animations Remove styles Lights Off
Close
AccessibilityContractsHomePhoto GalleryPrivacy & Refund PolicySitemapThank YouAbout UsOur TeamContactCanineEquineFoalsLaboratoryStallionsDirections
